<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jan Michael Laranjo</title>
    <description>Computer Science Student at University of Technologies Vienna</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Update</title>
        <description>
          
          layout: post title: “Life Update” subtitle: “Giving an update about my current life situation” — Hey, I haven’t been posting for such a long time. So much happened since my last post. Therefore, I want to give you a short update in my life. First of all, I have a...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-10-06-life-update/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-10-06-life-update/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Life Update</title>
        <description>
          Some current status update - 
          Today I want to to give a brief status update of my life because, since my last post, some major changes have occured. Last semester of my studies was a huge progress towards achieving my bachelor degree. It was the most productive semester ever. I achieved 32,5 ects while working...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-03-15-life-update/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-03-15-life-update/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding Colleagues</title>
        <description>
          Why is it important to find reliable colleagues at universities - 
          Intro For my first post I want to address an important aspect which can avoid a lot of trouble for any kind of student during their whole academic path. Recently I’ve had a discussion about group projects with a fellow. We talked about how much trouble we could have avoided,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018-12-08-group-work-in-university/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018-12-08-group-work-in-university/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>
          My first post about my intentions for the blog - 
          Hi. As you have noticed, this is my first blog post and I want to take this moment to introduce myself even though I provided a resume. Finally I want to tell you my intentions for this blog and what I want to write about. I am nearly done with...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2018-08-31-first-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018-08-31-first-post/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
